MIRANDA SÁNCHEZ

sanchezmiranda078@gmail.com | 1138905121 | Buenos Aires, Argentina

PROFILE

Graduate Student in **English-Spanish Certified Translation**, having passed 30 out of 32 courses, and specializing in legal, economic, financial, medical, and technical texts. Graduate **Computer Science** student and frontend programmer with two years of experience. Great creative capacity with an eye for detail. Solid communication and teamwork skills.

Fast learner with a strong commitment to further improving in both fields.

My portfolio: https://miranda-sanchez-portfolio.netlify.app/



linkedin.com/miranda--sanchez



github.com/miranda-sanchez

SKILLS

- CAT tools: Wordfast and Trados.
- **Design:** Photoshop and Illustrator.
- Programming: HTML5, CSS3, ReactJS, LESS, SASS, JavaScript, Git, GitHub, Jira, Figma, Bootstrap, SEO, PPO, MySQL.
- Microsoft Office: Advanced Word and PowerPoint, and intermediate Excel.
- Illustration and painting.

CERTIFICATES

Frontend Development Program at EducaciónIT: Web Development with HTML, Advanced Web Layout Design, Introduction to Object Oriented Programming, Git: Collaborative Design, Responsive Web y Bootstrap, Javascript for Advanced Developers

Advanced Program of French at Centro Universitario de Idiomas: Levels 1 to 6.

Superior Program of Portuguese at Centro Universitario de Idiomas: Level 1.

First Certificate in English, Cambridge

LANGUAGES

• Spanish: Native

• English: C2 (Bilingual)

• French: B1

• Portuguese: A1

EDUCATION

6-YEAR GRADUATE DEGREE IN ENGLISH-SPANISH CERTIFIED TRANSLATION

University of Buenos Aires

2019 - Present GPA: 8.70/10

5-YEAR GRADUATE DEGREE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Universidad Nacional del Oeste

2024 - Present

4-YEAR GRADUATE DEGREE IN GRAPHIC DESIGN

University of Buenos Aires

2018 (Incomplete)

WORK EXPERIENCE

TRANSLATION FOR A PRIVATE CLIENT

Freelance: 2022

 Spanish to English translation of a ceramist's cover letter to be submitted to the International Academy of Ceramics.

FRONT-END DEVELOPER

Freelance: 2022 - Present

• Frontend development of responsive web pages using ReactJs. In charge of UX design and component development from scratch.

ENGLISH TEACHER

Freelance: 2019 — Present

 Remote English classes for students with different levels of proficiency. Lesson planning and correction.

CUSTOMER SERVICE

2019 - 2021

 Personalized attention and advice to customers in a retail clothing store. Management of product returns and exchanges.